askbaby.com 2013-12-25

# Privacy Policy - Your personal information and us....

Your personal information and us.

Here at AskBaby.com we take your privacy very seriously, this Privacy Policy sets out how we will treat your personal information. Please familiarise yourself with the information below before using or submitting information to the site.

**Your permission**

By using AskBaby.com and submitting information to the site you are agreeing to the information set out in our Terms and Conditions and our Privacy Policy. 

**The information we collect**

AskBaby.com may collect, store and use the following personal information from you: 

  * Information about your computer and about your visits to and use of the website. This may include information about the length of your visit, page views, your IP address, browser type, geographical location and referral source.
  * Information that you provide to us in your AskBaby profile, including your email address.
  * Any other information that you choose to share with us including posts made in our chat rooms, forums and comments boxes.

**Cookies**

AskBaby.com use cookies on the website, these are text files sent by a web server to a web browser, which are then stored by the browser. To enable the web server to identify and track the browsers activity this text file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. 

We will send cookies to your computer in order to enable AskBaby.com to identify you when you are logged in, to manage your sessions on the website, to monitor and log your activity on AskBaby.com. Cookies may be stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Most browsers enable you to refuse cookies however this often has a negative impact on the usability of many websites. 

**Your personal information**

Any information you submit to AskBaby.com will be used for purposes set out in the Privacy policy or as otherwise specified on the website. To this end we may use your personal information to enable your use of the website, improve your browsing experience (by personalising and extending the functionality of the website), manage any competition entries you submit and to send you the AskBaby.com newsletter (if this is something you have requested). 

Personal information may be shared with contractors used to support AskBaby.com. However, third parties will be required to treat member information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Please visit [www.otpmedia.com/privacy](http://www.otpmedia.com/privacy) to view the privacy policy of our advertising agency, Otp-Media. 

We will not share your personal information with third parties for the purpose of direct marketing. 

We may however provide third parties with statistical information about AskBaby.com users, this information will not be used to identify any one user. 

Additionally, when entering a competition on AskBaby.com if you register your interest in any of the companies displayed after you have submitted your entry you are agreeing for your details to be shared with those third parties selected and for them to contact you in due course. 

We may also use your personal information to deal with enquiries and complaints relating to AskBaby.com (made by or about you) and to investigate any misuse or alleged misuse of the website. This includes disclosing information about you if we are required to do so by law, in connection with any current or prospective legal proceedings and in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights. 

**International data transfers**

It is possible that information collected from AskBaby.com may be stored, processed in and transferred between the countries in which we operate so that we are able to use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**Security**

AskBaby.com take both technical and organisational precautions to prevent any loss, misuse or alteration of the personal information you share with us. Any information you share with us will be stored in a password-protected database and our servers are protected by a firewall. 

You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. 

**Public information**

AskBaby.com allows members to post in forums, chat rooms and on certain pages throughout the site. Please be aware that any comments you make will be viewed publicly so do be careful what information you disclose. 

**Third party websites**

AskBaby.com does contain links to third party websites however we are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of these other sites. 

**Updating information**

Please keep the account information held in your AskBaby.com profile up-to-date. You can amend the information held by AskBaby.com by logging into the site and visiting the 'My Profile' page. 

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time and a revised version will be posted on this page. For this reason we recommend that you check this page occasionally to ensure that you are happy with any amendments. 

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about the AskBaby.com Privacy Policy or our treatment of your personal information, please get in touch either by using our [contact us form](http://www.askbaby.com/contact-us.htm) or by writing to AskBaby.com, c/o Dot Zinc Limited, Fleet House, 8-12 New Bridge Street, London, EC4V 6AL.
